Previously on AMC's "The Walking Dead"...
《行尸走肉》前情提要
We are the ones who get things done.
我們是能做成事的人
We can find a way to beat them.
我們能找到戰勝他們的方法
Tara, you've been out further than any of us.
塔拉  你在外面比我們走得都遠
The least you can tell is where not to look.
至少你能告訴我們別去哪找
Yeah.
好的
Sure thing.
當然
Don't do this.
別這樣做
We need to wait for the right moment.
我們要等待合適的時機
Guns.
槍
A lot.
很多槍
And then we fight your fight.
拿到后我們會加入你的戰斗
Yes.
好的
We have a deal.
達成協議了
Thanks for keeping watch last night.
謝謝你昨晚守夜
Oh, it's nothing. I like it.
沒事  我喜歡
Uh, you can keep watch tonight.
今晚你來守吧
We gonna win today?
我們今天會有收獲嗎
Oh, yeah.
會的
We're gonna need batteries for that walkie, too.
我們也需要給那個對講機找電池
Get it working again.
讓它重新開始工作
What is it? What's that smile?
怎么了  笑什么
Couple of days out, all we got to show are
我們出來幾天了  結果只找到
two guns, dented cans of beans,
差不多兩把槍  幾個壓扁的豆子罐頭
and some football jerseys, pretty much.
和幾件球衣
Pretty much.
差不多吧
We're fightin' the fight.
我們在抗爭
It's better.
這樣更好
Good morning.
早上好
And if I hear one more goddamn word about Fat Joey,
如果我再聽見關于肥喬的一個字
I'm gonna smash somebody's teeth in.
我就要打碎某人的牙齒
Good riddance to dead weight.
我看是甩掉了累贅
No more mascot crap.
總算沒什么狗屁吉祥物了
They got good taste in pretzels.
他們對椒鹽脆餅的品位不錯
And batteries.
還有電池
Two days. We're gonna need to get back.
兩天了  我們得回去了
Rick...
瑞克
Day and a half more -- today and tomorrow.
再過一天半  今天和明天
We can come out again. We should get back.
我們可以再出來  我們應該回去了
Just a little more.
再轉會兒
We're okay.
我們沒事
We don't have to find them right now.
我們沒必要現在就找到武器
Yeah, I know.
我知道
Just a little more, okay?
再轉轉吧
Okay.
好
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
最新連載海外影視劇下載 請登陸 www.YYeTs.com 僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
Hey, I was just coming over to do that.
我正想來拆線
Denise showed me how.
丹妮斯教過我
I'm done.
我弄完了
What?
怎么了
Nothing.
沒什么
Okay.
好吧
It's gonna work out.
時間軸     加森  濤濤
What -- What does that even mean, Tara?
那是什么意思  塔拉
It means we've got the numbers to fight now.
后期     送小哥  拉圖
We just need to find some guns and --
我們只用找一些槍
Do you know where we could find that many guns today?
你知道我們今天能在哪找到這么多槍嗎
This week? This year?
這周呢  今年呢
No. You don't.
你不知道
I can't just wait.
我不能就這樣等著
I don't know about you, but I can't.
我不知道你  但我不行
We're gonna find the guns, okay? And we're gonna fight.
我們會找到槍的  好嗎  我們會戰斗的
Look, it's not gonna be easy.
這肯定不容易
It wasn't the last time at the outpost.
不像上次哨站那樣
Hey, maybe you could just save all this for them.
也許你可以省點脾氣跟他們打
Here.
給
It'll help with your scar.
能幫你的傷疤愈合
Keep it.
你留著吧
We need guns.
我們需要槍
I'm gonna go find them.
我要去找
Damn it.
該死
What was it?
怎么了
It was a deer.
是一頭鹿
I owe you a deer.
我欠你一頭鹿
From before.
之前那次
When they were outside the gate.
當時他們在門外
Oh, yeah, you do.
是啊
You see that?
看見了嗎
Yeah.
嗯
It's guns like that. That's why we're out here.
這種槍就是我們出來要找的
Something serious happened here.
這里發生了慘劇
A long time ago.
很久以前
Yeah. These are serious rounds.
是啊  這些子彈很不錯
Might be serious guns here, too.
也許這里也有好槍
Let's get a better look.
我們上去瞧瞧
Yeah.
好
Damn it.
該死
Watch your step.
注意腳下
Maybe we shouldn't be up here too long.
也許我們不該在這里待太久
Well, let's see what we're gonna see.
我們去看看有什么吧
Soldiers, civilians, all those rounds --
士兵  平民  這些子彈
There was a fight.
曾有一場惡戰
Maybe it was the walkers.
也許是行尸
Maybe just other people.
也許是別的人
They're still wearing their guns.
他們還背著槍
I think this is it.
我覺得就是這里了
I think it is, too.
我也這么想
Think we can?
覺得我們可以搞定嗎
Yeah, we can.
可以的
Are you okay?
你沒事吧
Y-Yeah. Are you?
沒事  你呢
I am. ?
我沒事
This is -- This is a sign, right?
這是個預兆  對吧
This is it. It has to be.
是的  肯定是
Oh-ho. It is.
的確是
Well, they're ready.
它們是即食的
Let's eat.
我們吃吧
I didn't find any guns.
我沒找到槍
In case you were wondering.
如果你想知道的話
I was out there all day and not a damn one.
我在外面找了一整天  一把都沒找到
Not a real one.
一把真槍都沒找到
Thing is, I had a gun.
問題是  我之前有一把槍
I was gonna use it to kill Negan.
我本來打算用它殺了尼根
I was ready to.
我都已經準備好了
And if I had done it, like I'd planned to,
假如我當時按計劃做了
Negan would be dead right now.
如今尼根已經死了
And, yeah, maybe I'd be dead, too, but who gives a damn?
沒錯  也許我也會死  但誰他媽在乎
Eugene would still be here.
那樣的話尤金就不會被抓走
Olivia would still be alive.
奧利維亞會活著
Spencer would still be alive.
斯賓塞也會活著
And now they're gone, and I'm here
但如今他們都不在了  我卻還在
because I was stupid enough to listen to you.
就因為我愚蠢地聽信了你的話
But you were.
但你聽了
And you did.
也照做了
You stand there telling people about their lives.
你就站在那里對別人指手畫腳
Only if they come here.
只對那些來這里的人
Like you.
比如你
Right now.
就像現在
You don't know shit about shit.
你什么都不懂
You're right.
你說得對
I don't.
我的確不懂
I said that you weren't supposed to die
我說過你不應該去送死
and that you shouldn't do the thing that you were planning to do
不應該去做那件你計劃要做的事
because we needed you --
因為我們需要你
still do.
我們如今依然需要
Even a fool like me could see that.
像我這樣的傻瓜都能看清那一點
It's easier to be dead,
死了的確更容易些
and if it's my fault you're alive,
假如你還活著是我的錯的話
well, I'm just gonna have to live with that.
那我只能背負著這個錯誤了
I decided to meddle.
我當時決定要插手
But I did something I thought was right,
但我做的是我認為正確的事
and I knew the stakes were very high.
我也知道這事風險很大
You can certainly blame me for the fact that you have a life,
你當然可以因為自己還活著而指責我
but after that what are you going to do with it?
但之后呢  你要怎么辦
How are you going to make what needs to happen happen?
你要如何促成那些必須發生的事
Anything is possible until your heart stops beating.
在你心跳停止之前  一切皆有可能
Certainly more than yelling at a fool.
你能做的絕不僅僅是沖著個傻子大吼
What?
什么
How is it?
如何
It's good.
棒極了
So, tomorrow...
所以  明天...
we go out there, we get the weapons, right?
我們出去  把武器搶回來  對嗎
We get Jadis and her people to fight with us.
然后讓簡迪斯和她的人跟我們一起戰斗
We kill Negan
我們殺死尼根
and anyone else we have to to win.
以及其他該殺之人  來贏得戰斗
And what happens after that?
在那之后呢
After that, we keep going.
之后  我們繼續生活
Yeah, but...
是的  但是
Negan ordered the world his way.
尼根用他的方法統治世界
It's up to us to reorder it once he's gone, right?
他死之后  我們應該建立新秩序  對吧
All the different communities,
所有社區
they can figure it out together, how to keep going together.
可以一起想辦法  討論如何繼續生活
Yeah, but somebody's gonna have to make that happen.
對  但總得有人促成這事
Somebody will need to be in charge of that, right?
總得有人負責  對嗎
It should be you.
那個人應該是你
- Not me. - ?Why not?
-不是我  -為什么
You could do it.
你可以勝任的
?You'd be good at it.
你會做得很好
I mean, if it's something that you wanted.
如果你想做的話
Well, I don't think I do. Or I would.
我不想做  也不愿意做
But the two of us, you and me,
但如果是咱們倆  你和我
reordering things together...
一起重建秩序
I want that.
那我愿意
If it's something you wanted....
假如你也愿意的話...
Yeah.
我愿意
I'm gonna eat five more of these dinners, okay?
我要再吃五包這個  好嗎
You know...
知道嗎
we don't have to get it done tomorrow.
我們用不著明天就搞定
We can take our time.
我們可以悠閑點
If we go another day, another one after that, it's fine.
過一兩天再走也沒關系
I mean, the place is clear.
我是說  這地方沒危險
It's locked up tight.
嚴嚴實實的
We found the only way in, so...
只有一條路能進來  所以
We should get back.
我們應該回去
If we're getting the guns,
既然能拿到槍
it doesn't matter if it takes a little longer.
多費點時間也沒關系
Wait. I've been, um...
等等  我一直
I've been waiting to show you this one.
在等著給你看這個
It's, um, chili and mac and cheese...
這可是  辣椒  奶酪意面
together.
大雜燴
Come on.
試試吧
Oh. Sorry.
抱歉
I was just thinking.
我在思考
W..you...you want this?
什么  你要這個
Congrats.
恭喜
It's yours.
歸你了
Someone gave it to me, someone who helped me.
是別人送我的  曾經幫助過我的某人
She put her ass on the line for me.
她為我不顧一切
She saved my life, you know?
她救了我的命  知道嗎
She didn't have to. But she did.
她本來不用做  但卻做了
That means something now -- it does. It has to.
如今這是有意義的  毋庸置疑
If I say something, you know --
要是我說了  知道嗎
Rick won't leave there without their guns.
拿不到槍  瑞克是不會離開那里的
If -- if we could even get close enough,
就算我們能成功接近那里
they'll start firing, and we'll fire back.
她們也會開火  我們會反擊
I mean, they should just fight with us.
她們應該跟我們并肩戰斗的
The Saviors killed their fathers
救世軍殺了她們的父親
and their sons and their brothers.
兒子和兄弟
They won't want to fight with us.
但她們不想和我們并肩戰斗
They just want to hide.
她們只想藏起來
So they'll just fight us.
所以她們只能和我們戰斗
I tell everyone about Oceanside, that's what happens.
如果我告訴大家海邊旅館的事  就會這樣
What makes our life worth more than theirs?
憑什么我們的命比他們的更珍貴
Because we want to stop
就因為我們想阻止
the people that are hurting us,
那些傷害我們的人嗎
who will hurt other people?
那些會傷害別人的人嗎
God damn it.
該死
Look.
看
The walkers in the field, they're not closed in.
行尸在外游蕩  沒有被關起來
Yeah.
是啊
We got to take care of the ones out here
我們得干掉外面的這些
and block that gap, too, so we can take the rest slow.
把缺口堵上  然后再慢慢干掉剩下的
Seven, eight...
七  八...
nine...
九
That car -- I can block it up.
我能用那輛車堵上
I can take out that one on the way.
我能干掉擋路的那一個
You draw the rest.
你把剩下的引開
You're leaving me eight.
你給我留了八個
We could shoot them,
我們可以朝它們開槍
but that would call the rest from the field.
但這樣會引來其余的行尸
This is about doing it quiet, with the sword.
得悄悄行動  用劍
You can handle eight.
八個對你來說不是問題
You got your eight walkers. I can push.
你已經干掉八個行尸了  我推得動
So can I.
我也行
You just worry about steering us in that gap.
你只要負責把車開到缺口就行
?Shit.
該死
The brakes don't work.
剎車壞了
Michonne, you good?
米瓊恩  你沒事吧
Yeah.
沒事
You?
你呢
I think we overshot it.
我覺得我們開過頭了
You think or you know?
你覺得還是你確定
I know.
我確定
It was a good plan, though.
不過這是個好計劃
It was a great plan.
這個計劃超棒
We'll do it here.
就在這里吧
Yeah.
好
Shit. It's not gonna hold.
該死  這攔不住它們
There it goes!
過來了
Split them off into smaller groups.
我們散開  減少它們的數量
The barriers might hold.
柵欄也許能擋住
You take slide, I take Ferris wheel?
你去滑梯  我去摩天輪
Or we could just go.
或者我們可以直接逃
- You want to go? ?- Nah. We can do this.
-你想逃嗎  -不  我們能搞定
Yeah, I know we can.
我知道我們能
How you doing?!
你那邊如何
Eight more!
還剩八個
How about you?
你呢
10!
十個
Rick!
瑞克
Michonne!
米瓊恩
I tried, but I still owe you one.
我試過了  但我還欠你一頭
I could've gone a couple more days.
我可以在外面多待幾天
I would've liked that.
我喜歡那樣
I haven't been sleeping.
我一直沒睡
Thinking about what we lost.
想著我們失去了什么
Thinking about my friends.
想著我的朋友們
Glenn saved me.
格倫救過我
Right at the start.
在最開始的時候
I couldn't save him.
而我沒能救他
It's normal.
這很正常
I know that.
我知道
Being stuck on it.
無法釋懷
We went through something.
我們經歷了一些事
This -- This doesn't cure it.
光這樣是不能釋懷的
Rick, I'm sorry.
瑞克  我很抱歉
We're gonna fight them.
我們要反抗他們
That's what happens next.
這就是接下來會發生的事
And we're gonna lose people,
我們會失去一些人
maybe a lot of them, maybe even each other.
也許是很多人  也許是對方
Even then, it'll be worth it.
即使那樣  也值得
When I thought that...
當我想到...
I can't lose you.
我不能失去你
You asked me
你問過我
what kind of life we had just surrendering.
放棄算怎么個活法
It wasn't -- It wasn't a life.
那不是生活
What we did back there,
我們在那里做的事
what we're doing now,
我們現在做的事
making a future for Judith
為朱迪思拼未來
and for Glenn and Maggie's baby,
為格倫和瑪姬的孩子拼未來
fighting the fight, that's living.
做出抗爭  這才叫生活
You showed me that.
這是你讓我知道的
You can lose me.
你可以失去我
- No. - ?Yes, you can.
-不  -你可以
I can lose you. ?
我也可以失去你
We can lose our friends, people we love.
我們可以失去朋友  愛的人
It's not about us anymore.
這不再是關乎我們了
It's about a future.
是關乎未來
And if it's me who doesn't make it,
如果我沒能活下來
you're gonna have to lead the others forward
你就必須帶領其他人前行
because you're the one who can.
因為你有這能力
But...
但是
how do you know?
你怎么知道
Because...
因為
you led me here.
你帶我走到了這里
Operational? All?
全都能用嗎
To the best of my knowledge, yeah.
據我說知能
May need some cleaning. We found supplies.
可能需要清理一下  我們找到了物資
Expect us?
要我們清理嗎
We cleaned some. We oiled some.
我們清理了一部分  上了油
You can do the rest. We do this together.
剩下的你們來  我們是合作關系
Yes, yes, but operational?
好的  但能用嗎
Well, you can fire a few. Try them out, if you like.
你可以開幾槍試試  如果你想的話
- How many? - 63.
-多少把  -63把
We made an inventory.
我們做了清單
No.
不
You mean the inventory?
你是說不要清單嗎
- Not enough. ?What? - Wha-- ?What are you talking about?
-不夠  -你說什么
You asked for a lot of guns. That's what this is.
你要很多槍  這就是很多槍
Enough to fight your fight. Us? Nearly twice.
要為你戰斗  我們需要兩倍的槍
Need nearly twice.
需要兩倍的槍
We've wasted enough time.
我們浪費夠多時間了
Let's go. Take our guns with us.
走吧  帶上槍
No.
不行
Our guns to take. Our deal still on.
槍是我們的  協議還沒結束
Not all of them.
你們不能全拿
We're keeping 10 for ourselves -- to find more.
我們留十把  為了找更多的槍
Five.
五把
10. ?6.
-十把  -六把
10. ?9.
-十把  -九把
And the cat back.
而且要歸還貓
20. I keep the cat.
二十把  貓歸我
We get you the guns. We fight together.
我們給你找到槍  然后一起戰斗
Say yes.
說同意
Yes.
同意
More soon, we'll fight.
盡快拿來更多槍  我們就戰斗
You get a few more days
再多等幾天
before "What happens next."
"接下來的事"就會發生
That's right.
沒錯
We'll find more, figure it out.
我們會找到更多槍  想辦法解決
Soon.
很快的
In a few more days.
再多等幾天
You all right?
你沒事吧
Yeah, yeah, I was just -- I was just coming over to see you.
沒事  我只是...正準備去找你
What's up?
怎么了
Have you seen Rosita?
你見到羅西塔了嗎
She didn't show for her guard shift this morning.
今早換崗她不在
She probably just went out looking for more.
她大概出去找槍了吧
Mm. Yeah.
好吧
Why were you --
你為什么...
Why were you coming by?
你為什么找我
I have something to tell you.
我要告訴你一些事
Are you here --
你來這里是...
I'm here because I need your help.
我來這里是找你幫忙的
One condition --
有一個條件
I get to take the shot.
要由我殺他
Okay.
好
Did you bring any explosives from the bridge?
你帶橋上的炸藥了嗎
I thought about it.
我考慮過
But I didn't want anyone finding out and trying to stop me.
但我不想被別人發現和阻止
I got something better, though.
我帶了更好的東西
So you can take your shot.
這樣你就能殺他了
Rick and Michonne found guns.
瑞克和米瓊恩找到了槍
But they aren't ready to move.
但他們沒準備好行動
They can't.
他們不能
The need more guns, more people, more time,
她們需要更多槍  更多人  更多時間
more excuses.
更多借口
I memorized everything Daryl and Carl told Rick
我記下了達里爾和卡爾給瑞克說的
about the inside of Negan's place.
尼根基地內部情況
Jesus made me a map of the outside.
耶穌給我畫了一張外圍的地圖
It's far away. It's well-defended.
非常遠  守衛森嚴
There's only two of us. You changing your mind?
-只有我們兩個人  -你要改主意嗎
I'm ready to kill him.
我準備好殺他了
But I need to make sure you know what this means.
但我要確認你知道這意味著什么
Do you?
你知道嗎
They can't catch us alive.
他們不能活捉我們
If they do, we give them something.
如果被抓住  就給了他們借口
It's a one-way ticket for both of us.
我們這是有去無回
If it is both of us.
假如我們都去的話
It is.
我們都去